ALBERT JOAN AGRAMONTE SUERO

February 27 extension, residential, Colinas del Oeste, house 77 & Santo Domingo

Dominican Republic & (809) · 854 · 1810

albertjohan2707@gmail.com

SOCIAL LINKS

Links GitHub, LinkedIn, Portfolio

PROFILE

I'm passionate about programming. As a software developer, I like to innovate and work as a team. In my experience, colleagues are the most important in the working environment.

I have worked on certain personal and professional projects, which have allowed me to gain experience dealing with code and other people.

I plan to give everything for the company that is working and thus give to demonstrate my full potential to get to know me and continue growing as a developer.

EDUCATION

Brigham Young school

Aug 2016

Bachelor

Here I took my bachelor's degree, where I obtained the basic knowledge of the English language.

Instituto Tecnológico de las Américas(ITLA)

Aug 2020

Technologist

Here I spent my entire career as a software developer.

EXPERIENCE

Camsoft

Jun 2023 - Present

junior Programmer

Santo Domingo

· In camsoft, I am as a junior programmer where I develop as fullstack. In it, I have to give everything for the whole, both backend and frontend.

Simetrica Consulting

Apr 2023 - Jun 2023

junior Programmer

Santo Domingo

· In this company I did my internship, in which I stood out as a backend developer, working in the c# and programming language. net framework. Where I made apis with my colleagues.

COURSES

 JavaScript - Udemy
 Jul 2022 - Aug 2022

 Node.js - Udemy
 Aug 2022 - Sept 2022

 Express.js - Udemy
 Oct 2022 - Dic 2022

 TailwindCss - Udemy
 Dic 2022 - Jan 2022

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

Computer LanguagesJavaScript, TypeScript, C#, PythonFrameworksTailwindCss, React, ExpressJs, .Net

Protocols & APIsJSON, RESTDatabasesMySQL, SqlServer

Tools Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Postman, Jira

Others Git, GitHub, GitLab, NodeJs, Html, Css

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Foundation Professional Certification - SFPC

Mar 2023 CertiProf

Scrum Foundation Professional Certification holders have developed entry-level skills in Scrum that endorse their fundamental knowledge in this framework.

REFERENCES

Oscar Encarnacion LizCoordinador de Incidentes ciberneticos CSIRT-RD(849) 655-1482Gabriel de los Santos SanchezAnalista de Incidentes ciberneticos(829) 807-8448